To Do:
----UNFINISHED----
*HIGH PRIORITY*
Add line following code (copy from theta?)

*MEDIUM PRIORITY*
Make the FSM synchronize better with autoReset()...
Monitor I/D of pots/encoders to detect when motor(s) is/are stuck.
Comment all functions!!!

*LOW PRIORITY*
Make emulated fake qse values go correct direction with motors.
Make emulated fake pot values (lift).
Change slew function from slew(curr,last,slew) to slew(diff,slew).



----FINISHED----
Make a Finite State Machine with a global "State".
Set all "last"s one time in the code (in a function).
Make more #define'd [modes] (competition, emulator, TEC), instead of [#define SIMULATOR].
Make all #defines in all caps with underscores FOR_EXAMPLE_THIS.
Put all initialization in one function.
Put constant loop time code in a function.
Make autonomous drivetypes.
Make min time and max time for steps and debug stream when min or max time used.
Make Motor targets variables, (motorLift=UP; OR motorLift=LIFT_TOP;).
Add auton processing code to output and assign auton inputs straight to motor target vars.
Add from Theta:
- Absolute gyro
- slew controllers
- No_pots btn
Make LCD backlight modes (Always on, Always off, Blinking slow, Blinking fast).
If emulated, then create fake qse values.
Put Sounds and Autonomous Files in subfolder (if possible).
If Cortex/power exp voltage is too low in auton: don't move, show LCD message, and beep.
Make joystick check function.
Give Motors names in motor test
Make checklist in lcd menu instead of motor enable toggle when competition is defined.
Change MODE to two defines, one for EMULATOR and one for COMPETITION.
Rename sysAutoStep to autoStep.
Make LCD modes look like each other.
Make the AutoReset action value jump to the wanted step.
Center auto selector pot (menu hint).
Make processLCD() and outputLCD().
Make TIME_LIMIT end type not trigger MIN_TIME.
Change statements in ZeroMotors() into a loop.
(BUG in operator control, it checks for lift output values, not for lift input values.)
Add sound FX capabilities.
Monitor time that controller has not been touched, and alert when 1 min passed.



----UNTESTED----
Add US sensor code.
Finish DRIVE_READY end type.
Fix sensor irregularities.
Create TOTAL_READY (or ROBOT_READY).
Make scripting built in.
